Guide to the Elizabeth S. Lyman Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Additional papers, Accession ARCH-1990-096
  - HUB Papers-Resource Files, Series 1
    - Women's Employment Education (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Women and Enterprise (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Weal MA (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Women for Economic Justice (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Women's Foundation (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Women's Funding Coalition (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Women's Business Owner's Educational Fund (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Women's Campaign Fund (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Women's Community Fund (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Women's Computer Literacy Project (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Women's Economic Development Corp. (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Women's Funding Coalition (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Women in Community Development (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Women in Financial Planning (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Women in Transition (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Women's Initiative Project (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Women's Institute for Housing (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Women for a Meaningful Summit (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Women's Research and Education Institute (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Women's Rights Information (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Women's Rights Law Reporter (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Women's Technical Institute (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Women's Therapy Centre Institute (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - WHO (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Working Women's Institute (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Working Women's Educational Fund (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Working Woman Mag. (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Worksteader News (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Wright Institute (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - MacDonald's Youth Enterprise Program Concept Prayer (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Youth Policy Institute (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Women's Business Council (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - ESL Papers - Orange Files
      - Hub Funding - The Aetna (Box 14, Folder 1)
      - Anheuser-Busch Companies, Inc. (Box 14, Folder 2)
      - Atlantic Richfield Fdn. (ARCO) (Box 14, Folder 3)
      - Mary Reynolds Babcock Fdn. (Box 14, Folder 4)
      - Tom Baillard (no folder) (Box 14, Folder 5)
      - Beatrice Foundation (Box 14, Folder 6)
      - Chase Bank (Box 14, Folder 7)
      - CBS Foundation (Box 14, Folder 8)
      - Chevron USA (Box 14, Folder 9)
      - Connecticut National Bank (Box 14, Folder 10)
      - Ann DeBusk (private contribution) (Box 14, Folder 11)
      - Equitable Life Assurance Soc. (Box 14, Folder 12)
      - Economic Develop. Admin. (Box 14, Folder 13)
      - Exxon Corp. (Box 14, Folder 14)
      - Ford Foundation (Box 14, Folder 15)
      - Fund for New Jersey (Box 14, Folder 16)
      - Gannett Foundation (Box 14, Folder 17)
      - German Marshall Fund (empty) (Box 14, Folder 18)
      - Glenmede Trust Co. (Box 14, Folder 19)
      - Robert Gries (empty) (Box 14, Folder 20)
      - Gund Foundation (empty (Box 14, Folder 21)
      - Hartford Foundation for Public Giving (empty) (Box 14, Folder 22)
      - Hearst Foundation (empty) (Box 14, Folder 23)
      - Hunt Alternatives (empty) (Box 14, Folder 24)
      - Johnson Foundation (empty) (Box 14, Folder 25)
      - Levi Strauss (empty) (Box 14, Folder 26)
      - Long Foundation (empty) (Box 14, Folder 27)
      - Met. Life Ins. Co. (empty) (Box 14, Folder 28)
      - Michigan Dept. of Commerce (empty) (Box 14, Folder 29)
      - Mobil Foundation (empty) (Box 14, Folder 30)
      - Mott: Flint (empty) (Box 14, Folder 31)
      - Mott: General Support (empty) (Box 14, Folder 32)
      - Newark Chamber of Commerce (empty) (Box 14, Folder 33)
      - New York Times Co. Foundation (empty) (Box 14, Folder 34)
      - Prudential - Alex Plinio (empty) (Box 14, Folder 35)
      - Ann Roberts (empty) (Box 14, Folder 36)
      - Rockefeller Family and Associates (empty) (Box 14, Folder 37)
      - Rockefeller Family Fund (empty) (Box 14, Folder 38)
      - Sears Roebuck and Co. (Box 14, Folder 39)
      - Travellers Ins. (empty) (Box 14, Folder 40)
      - Victoria Foundation (empty) (Box 14, Folder 41)
      - Women's Bureau (U.S. Labot Dept.) (empty) (Box 14, Folder 42)
      - Westinghouse Electric Corp. (empty) (Box 14, Folder 43)
      - Dr. Marilyn Yalom (empty) (Box 14, Folder 44)
    - ESL Papers - Sara Gould - Green Files
      - Transfer Payment Investment (Box 15, Folder 1)
      - UN Nongovtmental Liason Serv (yellow label) (Box 15, Folder 2)
      - West German Trip (yellow label) (Box 15, Folder 3)
      - Wharton: Lyman etc. (Box 15, Folder 4)
      - NYRAG Panel - Ms. foundation (blue label) (Box 15, Folder 5)
      - [UNLABELED] (Box 15, Folder 6)
      - [Displaced Homemaker's Network (loose)] (Box 15, Folder 7)
      - First Nations Financial Report (Box 15, Folder 8)
      - Wisconsin Conference - SKG (Box 15, Folder 9)
      - [Wisconsin Strategic Development Commission: Final Report (loose)] (Box 15, Folder 10)
      - [Wisconsin Dept. of Development (loose)] (Box 15, Folder 11)
      - Struggling Through Tight Times (Box 15, Folder 12)
      - Coastal Enterprises (Box 15, Folder 13)
      - Displaced Homemakers (Box 15, Folder 14)
      - Displaced Homemakers Project - Maine (Box 15, Folder 15)
      - SKG: Women's Economic Dev. Corp. (Box 16, Folder 1)
      - [Women's Technical Institute (loose)] (Box 16, Folder 2)
      - [Speak Out (loose)] (Box 16, Folder 3)
      - [Women's Entrepreneurial and Job Development Program Final Report (1980) (loose)] (Box 16, Folder 4)
      - [Women and Appropriate Technology (loose)] (Box 16, Folder 5)
      - [Women and Technology, Deciding What's Appropriate (loose)] (Box 16, Folder 6)
      - Bitterroot Educational Resources for Women (Box 16, Folder 7)
      - Campaign for Human Development (Box 16, Folder 8)
      - TAWG (Box 16, Folder 9)
      - Tribal Sovereignty Program (red label) (Box 16, Folder 10)
      - Tufts University - Schramm (Box 16, Folder 11)
      - Wider Opportunities for Women (Box 16, Folder 12)
      - SKG: Wisconsin CDFA (Box 16, Folder 13)
      - Wisconsin Women's Council (Box 16, Folder 14)
      - Stephanie Smith - Law Center (Box 16, Folder 15)
      - Miscellaneous Women's Groups (Blue) (Box 17, Folder 1)
      - Resume (Box 17, Folder 2)
      - National Congress (Box 17, Folder 3)
      - Industrial Cooperative Assoc. (Box 17, Folder 4)
      - International Tribune Center (Box 17, Folder 5)
      - Mainstay Inc. (yellow label) (Box 17, Folder 6)
      - Massachusetts Governor's Office (Box 17, Folder 7)
      - Midwest Women's Center (Box 17, Folder 8)
      - [National Economic Development and Law Center (letter) (loose)] (Box 17, Folder 9)
      - National Network of Hispanic Women (Box 17, Folder 10)
      - SKG: Navaho Tribe (Box 17, Folder 11)
      - OECD (Box 17, Folder 12)
      - REFUGEE Women - Sima Wali (Box 17, Folder 13)
      - Southeast Women's Emp. Coalition (Box 17, Folder 14)
      - [National Economic Develop. and Law Center (loose reports)] (Box 17, Folder 15)
      - Joan Sweeney (Box 17, Folder 16)
      - SKG: Survey Papers (Box 17, Folder 17)
      - [Mainstream Access Inc. (loose)] (Box 18, Folder 1)
      - Single HH Testimony (Box 18, Folder 2)
      - NYU Colloquium [sic]: E.D. Forwhem (Box 18, Folder 3)
      - Levi Strauss Project Mass. Women's Office (Box 18, Folder 4)
      - Ms. Foundation Briefing (Box 18, Folder 5)
      - N.Y. State Dept. of Ed. (Box 18, Folder 6)
      - SKG: Personal (Box 18, Folder 7)
      - [American Enterprise Institute for Public Policy Research (loose)] (Box 18, Folder 8)
      - SKG: AEI Corporate Meeting (Box 18, Folder 9)
      - SKG Cleveland Briefing (yellow label) (Box 18, Folder 10)
      - Hunt-Denver Meeting (Box 18, Folder 11)
      - December 11, 1985 Workshop (Box 18, Folder 12)
      - Montana Conference (Box 18, Folder 13)
      - SKG: Independent Sector (Box 18, Folder 14)
      - CfED: Hub Review Process (Box 19, Folder 1)
      - SKG: Correspondence (Box 19, Folder 2)
      - SKG: Fundraising (Box 19, Folder 3)
      - SKG: Hub Program Nat'l Budget (Box 19, Folder 4)
      - SKG: Job Training Partn. Act (Box 19, Folder 5)
      - UNLABELED (Box 19, Folder 6)
      - CfED general (Box 19, Folder 7)
      - Hub Funding and Cash Status (Box 19, Folder 8)
      - CfED Administrative Material (Box 19, Folder 9)
      - CfED Board Retreat (Box 19, Folder 10)
      - CfED Staff Meetings (Box 19, Folder 11)
      - CfED Women's Enterprise Development (Box 19, Folder 12)
      - CfED Women's Enterprise Development (Box 19, Folder 13)
      - CfED Strategy Committee (Box 19, Folder 14)
      - CfED Strategic Planning (yellow label) (Box 19, Folder 15)
      - UNLABELED (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - ESL Papers - Sara Gould - Misc. Files
      - UNLABELED (Box 20, Folder 1)
      - Sara's W. German Workshop (yellow label) (Box 20, Folder 2)
      - UNLABELED (Box 20, Folder 3)
      - Sara Gould (Box 20, Folder 4)
      - SKG: Women for Economic Justice (green label) (Box 20, Folder 5)
      - Working Guide (red) (Box 20, Folder 6)
      - Sara Gould Misc. Correspondence (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Unfoldered (Box 21)
    - Unfoldered (Box 22)
    - Unfoldered (Box 23)
    - Unfoldered (Box 24)
    - Unfoldered (Box 25)
    - Unfoldered (Box 26)
    - Unfoldered (Box 27)
    - Unfoldered (Box 28)
    - Unfoldered (Box 29)
  - Wingspread Working Guide Strategy Session, Series 2
    - Wingspread Travel Arrangements (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Wingspread Travel Expenses (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Wingspread Participant Response "Most Important Themes" (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Wingspread Participant List (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Wingspread Originals (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Wingspread Agenda and Small Group (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Wingspread Discussion Paper Final and Complete (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Wingspread Discussion Paper Comm. (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Wingspread Working Paper Comments (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Wingspread Working Paper on Women and Enterprise Development 5/13/85 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Wingspread Follow-up (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Wingspread Steering Committee (follow-up) (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Wingspread Journal Article 12/2/85 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - SKG Wingspread Follow-up (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - The Famous 2 Paragraphs (describing Wings. and Work. Guide) (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Wingspread Strategy Session Report Description of Participants (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Wingspread Report - Draft and Final (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Wingspread Report SKG (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - 8/7 Memo to Participants (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - To Receive Wingspread Report (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Wingspread Executive Summary (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - SKG: Wingspread (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Wingspread Attendees (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - People to Receive "Working Guide" (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Working Guide Background and Related Material (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Reactions to the Working Guide (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Working Guide Draft 2nd draft 11/86 (99% complete) (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Working Guide Advisory Committee (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Working Guide Drafts (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - 8/11/86 Working Guide Memo and Enclosures (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - List of People Who Received Working Guide Draft (1st draft) (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Working Guide Drafts and Notes (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Working Guide Contracts (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Working Guide News Release (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Working Guide: Sections Sent 12/16/86 w/memo (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Working Guide: 12/23/86 Draft (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Working Guide Partial Draft (1/15/87) (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Working Guide Revision as Sent to Sara and CfED 2/11/87 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Working Guide Reprinting Request - Metropolitan Life (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - EDA/Flow Chart - Sent to EDA for Working Guide (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Working Guide - - Final Draft (almost) (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Working Guide Draft - Confidential not for copying (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - SKG: Economic Development Admin. (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Draft Version 2/27/87 Office Copy for copying only (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Working Guide/EDA Financial Info. (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - EDA Proposal 3/85 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Sara's Chapter (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - EDA Jan '87 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Wingspread Misc. (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Hub Archives, Series 3
    - To Mail '81 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - 1982 - ESL - Reimbursement (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - AIS -- Reimbursement '83 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - '83 (no label) (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - '83 (no label) (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - '83 (no label) (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - '83 (no label) (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Misc. Reimbursements '83 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Funding Info. '83-'84 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - ESL Accounts 3/83 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - 4/30/83 (no label) (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - 5/8/83 Hub Internal Articles on Hub or WWW (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Reading 5/17/83 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - The Washington Post 6/19/83 "What Does Guilty Mean in the Second the Bullet Flies." (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Hub Internal - Correspondence in Reaction to Hub 7/20/83 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Hub Internal Gen'l Info. 8/24/83 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Hub Local Site Functions 8/25/83 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Hub Admin. Asst. Potential Also Econ Developer 9/16/83 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Hub External Contacts and Ideas 10/3/83 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - (no label) 10/12/83 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Hub-Hartford Staffing 10/19/83 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Hub Internal CfED description and 501(c)(3) 11/1/83 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - (no label) 12/83 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - (no label) 12/83 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - CfED - Funding 12/14/83 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Hub Advisory Comm. 11/28/83 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - (no label) '84 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - (no label) '84 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - 1984 CfED/Hub Reimbursement (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - 1984 Bethune Museum and Arch. Reimbursement (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - 1984 Reimbursement - CROW (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - WOW: Advisory Comm. Reimbursement 1984 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Working Assets Mgmt. Inc. Reimbursement 1984 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Schlesinger Library Reimbursement 1984 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Reimbursement Summary Sheets 1984 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Misc. Reimbursement 1984 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - To be Purchased 1984 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Budgets/Accounting P. Nolan 1984 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Photocopies Needed 1984 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Get to Later 1984 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Filing 2/84 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - 30733 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - CfED 1/9/84 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Hub Monthly Reports 3/2/84 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Hub 1984 Proposal to Joan Sweeney 3/13/84 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Conf. I Participants 3/23/84 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Hub Internal Finance 3/28/84 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - State Initiatives on Women and the Economy 4/2/84 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Needs Reimbursement - ESL 4/6/84 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Independent Sector Publications (cont.) 4/26/84 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - 31173 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Hub Job Application 5/7/84 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Hub Reimbursable Expenses 5/9/84 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - 1984: Enterprise Foundation Reimbursement (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Business and Professional Women's Foundation 85 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - 1985: Phone Messages Loose Scratch Paper (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Telecommunications Cooperative Network 1985 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Speech Folder - 11/29/85 - Nat. Conf. of Catholic Charities (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - People to Receive Hartford Report 1985 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Hub Funding 1985-1987 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - BPW U.S.A. Co-Venture (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - 31156 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - New York Times Article: (5/5/85) Responses (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Newspaper Art-Business 5/13/85 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - State Senator, Velmanette Montgomery 5/14/85 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Hartford Conf. Reimbursements 6/15/84 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Houston: Cleo Glenn Johnson 8/85 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Virginia Littlejohn 9/19/85 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Speech Folder - NNHW LA 11/1/85 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Susan Hager 11/19/85 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - CfED Board 12/11/85 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Outreach - Hub Process 12/17/85 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Support Services Survey 1986 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Hub Budget 86-87 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Co-venture Ann Roberts 1/3/86 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Salary Spreading: Instructions sent to D.H. 1/14/86 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Co-venture WOW: 1/24/86 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - AEI: Best Practices on Econ. Develop. 1/29/86 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Women-in-Business Inquiries 2/3/86 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Congressional Contacts 2/4/86 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Co-Ventures - Shared Space 2/4/86 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Hub Harvard Review Article 2/7/86 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - 31463 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Minnesota 2/27/86 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - ESL Co-Ventures 3/7/86 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Send Info. Packs 3/16/86 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Don Moss-letterhead 3/20/86 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Potential Funders: Hub-Co 3/21/86 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - AAUW - Co-Venture 3/23/87 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Hub Info Inquiries: 3/26/86 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Hub Program for Women's Enterprise 4/7/86 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Co-Venture: Hub - Jr. League 5/9/86 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Jean H. Hub Co - Enterprise 6/5/86 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Business Plan 6/6/86 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Highlights 6/9/86 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Outdated Position Descriptions 6/13/86 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Hub Co-Venture Job Applicants 6/13/86 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Packet to be Included in General Proposal 6/20/86 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - HEDCO Letter of Support 6/26/86 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Trip Folder - Wash. D.C. 6/30/86 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Possible Candidates for Consideration in EO Underclass Project 7/23/86 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - European Women's Management Development Network 7/26/86 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Expense Reimb. WEAL 7/28/86 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - White House Conf. on Small Business 8/17-21/86 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Watermark Association of Artisans 9/25/86 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Enabling Environment Conf. Nairobi, Kenya 10/86 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Hub: Co-Ventures - Funders: 10/29/86 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Proposal Abstract: 11/86 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Hub Process Summary: 11/86 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Advisory Committee: 11/86 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Anne de Busk 11/13/86 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Projects: 11/25/86 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Resumes Received November 1986 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Jing Lyman Ford: 12/3/86 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - ESL Income: 1986 Archive 12/19/86 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - 1987: Budget and Assumptions (old) (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Manchester Work Fold: 1987 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - 1987 Proposal Plan Report (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - ESL Event and Org. Sponsorship 1987 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - 1987 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Proposals Supporting Appendices ESL: 1987 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - New York City Commission on the Status of Women (Arch.) 1987 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - 31778 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Hub Update 1/87 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Working Guide Final 2/87 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Hub Co-Venture Fact Sheet as Prepared 5/18/87 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Dept. of Employment, U.K. Government 6/19/87 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Hub Proposal 7/87 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - General Corresp. Hub 7/87 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Summary as Used for Proposals 7/87 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Hub Proposals 7/8/87 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Welfare Issues 8/87 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Hub Archives: 3/29/88 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Sources of Job Applicants June 1988 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - 32325 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Unfoldered (Box 7)
    - Unfoldered (Box 8)
    - Unfoldered (Box 9)
    - Unfoldered (Box 10)
    - Unfoldered (Box 11)
    - Unfoldered (Box 12)
    - Unfoldered (Box 13)
    - Unfoldered (Box 14)
    - Unfoldered (Box 15)
    - Unfoldered (Box 16)
    - Unfoldered (Box 17)
    - Unfoldered (Box 18)
  - Foundation Center, Series 4
    - Foundation Center-Nom. Comm. 11/9/78 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - 1979 Foundation Center (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Foundation Center 5/10/79 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Foundation Center Board 11/8/79 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Foundation Center Leaflets (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Foundation Center SF Field Office (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Foundation Center 1980 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Foundation Center Exec. and Bd. Meet. 10-11/80 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Foundation Center 1981 Exec. Comm., Fin. and Audit Comm. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Foundation Center Jan-Aug 1981 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Foundation Center Sept.-Dec 1981 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - UNLABELED (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Foundation Center - WYE Conf. Aspen Institute (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - 1981 Foundation Center Board of Trustees (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - 1981 Foundation Center Chair's File (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - [loose material] (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Foundation Center 5/4/81 Corporate Services (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Foundation Center - Com. on Corp. Services 1981 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Con F FDN. CTR Legislative (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - 1982 Foundation Center Finance and Exec. Comm. (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - [loose material] (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - 4/15/82 Foundation Center Exec. Comm. Meeting (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - 5/13/82 Foundation Center Board Meeting (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - WAF/CP and Hub - Donors and Resources, Series 5
    - Clippings - Women In Enterprise (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - WAF/CP American Women in Russia (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - WAF/CP Kristin Anderson (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - WAF/CP Appalachian Foundation (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - WAF/CP Bank Street (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - WAF/CP Assoc. of Blk. Fdn. Execs. (ABFE) (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - WAF/CP Association of Junior Leagues Inc. (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - WAF/CP Judith Bardwick (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Black, Corrine (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - WAF/CP Bay Area Corp. 2% Club (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - WAF/CP Meredith Brokaw (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Hub - Brown and Dunkle (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - WAF/CP Rena Button (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - CBS Foundation (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - WAF/CP Celebrate Women (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Hub Center for Women in Government (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - WAF/CP Chart (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Chicago Council on Foreign Relations (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - WAF/CP Committee of 200 P. Clotherty and S. Davis (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - WAF/CP Community Fdn of Santa Clara County (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - WAF/CP Consulting Foundations (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - WAFCP Cooperating Organizations (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Corporate Philanthropy (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - WAF/CP Council on Foundations (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - WAF/CP Council of Churches of City of N.Y. Elna Seabrooks (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Hub Day Care (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - WAF/CP Department of Labor (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - WAF/CP Direct Selling Association (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - WAF/CP Domestic Violence (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - WAF/CP Edges Group, Inc. (10/6/81) (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Eisile, Karen (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Hub - Entrepreneurship Inst. Project Need-It (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - WAF/CP The Exchange Report Women in Third World (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - WAF/CP Equal Rights Advocates (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - WAF/CP Far West Labs (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - WAF/CP Ford Study (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - WAF/CP Ford Foundation (Issues) (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Fdn. Annual Reports (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - WAF/CP 1000 Friends of Oregon (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Friends of the American Museum in Britain (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - [Unlabeled] Funding Feminists (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - WAF/CP Funding Feminists (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - WAF/CP Tracy Gary (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - WAF/CP German Marshall Fund (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - WAF/CP Pat Graham (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - WAF/CP Grantsmanship Center (Box 3, Folder 14)